In today's video we are going to talk about 12 companies
in which we are
also going to cover those companies which are going to announce
dividend, stock split or results tomorrow.
So the
name of the company on the first number is III R Limited and the
stock of the company is currently trading
at ₹1722. So the company has announced a dividend of ₹,
which is going to be the final dividend
because this is the final
dividend, that is why its recorded amount has
not come yet. As soon as the company announces it, we will
update you. The rest of the company has
also announced the results. You can get the results of the companies on
our telegram.me
and the stock of the company is currently trading, so the
company is going to announce the dividend and
results on 24th of
April. So the name of the company on the sixth number
is 361 M Limited and the stock of the company is
currently
trading at ₹7789. So the company is going to announce the dividend and
results on 23rd of
April. The name of the company on the seventh number is
Esq Kubta Limited.  And the stock of the company is currently trading
at ₹ 62, so the company is going to announce dividend and
results on 9th
of May. So now let's talk about those companies
which are going to announce
dividend and results etc. tomorrow i.e. on 19th of April.
So the
name of the company is at 8th number, so the
company is going to announce dividend and results on
19th of
April. So the name of the company at 10th number is
Premier Explosives Limited and the stock of the company is going to announce results on
19th of
April. So the name of the company at 12th number is
Devangi Sugar Company Limited and the
stock of the company is currently trading at 84, so the company
is going to announce stock split and the
meeting of the board of directors of the company is going to be held on 19th of
April. If you liked the video, then do
like the video.